A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Washington, DC, Series O FA350
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Special Assistant to the President for Foreign Affairs (SAP), December 1954-December 1955; 7; 14.4 Cubic Feet
  - "Fortune Magazine", April 1941 (Box 202A, Folder 1789)
    Removed from Box 96, Folder 725.
  - Autographed Elephant (Box 202A, Folder 1790)
    Removed from Box 97, Folder 762.
- Presidential Mission to Latin America, May-July 1969; 8; 42.6 Cubic Feet
  The day after his inauguration, President Richard M. Nixon requested that Rockefeller consult with the leaders of the Latin American republics and determine the needs and conditions of those countries. In four separate trips during 1969, Rockefeller and a team of advisors visited 20 South American, Central American, and Caribbean republics. His advisors represented the fields of labor, cultural affairs, urban affairs, women's affairs, youth, media, finance and economics, and private enterprise. While Mr. Rockefeller met with the head of state and foreign minister of each country, the advisors met with public and private representatives of their respective fields. This subseries includes briefing books on each country provided by the U.S. Department of State, correspondence with Latin American and U.S. ambassadors, country reports prepared by the advisors, Rockefeller's notes from his meetings with heads of state, and drafts of the final report to Congress and President Nixon. (Note: Some documents in this subseries bear U.S. government security classifications and therefore remain closed.)
  - Argentina - Follow-up Correspondence (Box 98, Folder 763)
  - Argentina - Adviser Reports (Box 98, Folder 764)
  - Argentina - Briefing Books (Box 98, Folder 765)
  - Argentina - Guest Lists (Box 98, Folder 766)
  - Argentina - Confederacin General Econmica materials (Box 98, Folder 767)
  - Argentina - NAR Notes (Box 98, Folder 768)
  - Argentina - Country Reports (Box 98, Folder 769)
  - Argentina - Documents (Box 98, Folder 770)
  - Barbados - Briefing Books (Box 98, Folder 771)
  - Barbados - Adviser Reports (Box 98, Folder 772)
  - Barbados - Schedules (Box 99, Folder 773)
  - Barbados - Documents (Box 99, Folder 774)
  - Barbados - NAR Notes (Box 99, Folder 775)
  - Barbados - Follow-up Correspondence (Box 99, Folder 776)
  - Barbados - Country Reports (Box 99, Folder 777)
  - Bolivia - Adviser Reports (Box 99, Folder 778)
  - Bolivia - Documents (Box 99, Folder 779)
  - Bolivia - Briefing Books (Box 99, Folder 780)
  - Bolivia - Country Reports (Box 99, Folder 781)
  - Bolivia - NAR Notes (Box 99, Folder 782)
  - Bolivia - Schedules (Box 99, Folder 783)
  - Bolivia - Follow-up Correspondence (Box 99, Folder 784)
  - Brazil - Briefing Books (Box 100, Folder 785)
  - Brazil - Schedules (Box 100, Folder 786)
  - Brazil - Country Reports (Box 100, Folder 787)
  - Brazil - Follow-up Correspondence (Box 100, Folder 788)
  - Brazil - Adviser Reports (Box 101, Folder 789)
  - Brazil - NAR Notes (Box 101, Folder 790)
  - Brazil - Documents (Box 101, Folder 791)
  - Brazil - Schedules (Box 101, Folder 792)
  - Brazil - Various Published Materials (Box 101, Folder 793)
  - Brazil - Various Published Materials (Box 101, Folder 794)
  - Chile - Briefing Books (Box 102, Folder 795)
  - Colombia - Briefing Books (Box 102, Folder 796)
  - Colombia - Country Reports (Box 102, Folder 797)
  - Colombia - Documents (Box 102, Folder 798)
  - Colombia - Follow-up Correspondence (Box 102, Folder 799)
  - Colombia - Schedules (Box 103, Folder 800)
  - Colombia - Advisers Reports (Box 103, Folder 801)
  - Colombia - NAR Notes (Box 103, Folder 802)
  - Costa Rica - Follow-up Correspondence (Box 103, Folder 803)
  - Costa Rica - Schedules (Box 103, Folder 804)
  - Costa Rica - NAR Notes (Box 103, Folder 805)
  - Costa Rica - Adviser Reports (Box 103, Folder 806)
  - Costa Rica - Documents (Box 103, Folder 807)
  - Costa Rica - Briefing Books (Box 103, Folder 808)
  - Costa Rica - Country Reports (Box 103, Folder 809)
  - Dominican Republic - Briefing Books (Box 103, Folder 810)
  - Dominican Republic - Country Reports (Box 104, Folder 811)
  - Dominican Republic - Schedules (Box 104, Folder 812)
  - Dominican Republic - NAR Notes (Box 104, Folder 813)
  - Dominican Republic - Adviser Reports (Box 104, Folder 814)
  - Dominican Republic - Follow-up Correspondence (Box 104, Folder 815)
  - Dominican Republic - Memorandum to NAR (Box 104, Folder 816)
  - Dominican Republic - Documents (Box 105, Folder 817)
  - Ecuador - Briefing Books (Box 105, Folder 818)
  - Ecuador - Country Reports (Box 105, Folder 819)
  - Ecuador - NAR Notes (Box 105, Folder 820)
  - Ecuador - Follow-up Correspondence (Box 105, Folder 821)
  - Ecuador - Documents (Box 105, Folder 822)
  - Ecuador - Adviser Reports (Box 105, Folder 823)
  - El Salvador - Adviser Reports (Box 105, Folder 824)
  - El Salvador - Follow-up Correspondence (Box 105, Folder 825)
  - El Salvador - Documents (Box 105, Folder 826)
  - El Salvador - Schedules (Box 106, Folder 827)
  - El Salvador - NAR Notes (Box 106, Folder 828)
  - El Salvador - Country Reports (Box 106, Folder 829)
  - El Salvador - Briefing Books (Box 106, Folder 830)
  - Guatemala - NAR Notes (Box 106, Folder 831)
  - Guatemala - Adviser Reports (Box 106, Folder 832)
  - Guatemala - Follow-up Correspondence (Box 106, Folder 833)
  - Guatemala - Country Reports (Box 106, Folder 834)
  - Guatemala - Documents (Box 107, Folder 835)
  - Guatemala - Briefing Books (Box 107, Folder 836)
  - Guyana - Briefing Books (Box 107, Folder 837)
  - Guyana - Documents (Box 107, Folder 838)
  - Guyana - Schedules (Box 107, Folder 839)
  - Guyana - Country Reports (Box 108, Folder 840)
  - Guyana - NAR Notes (Box 108, Folder 841)
  - Guyana - Advisers Reports (Box 108, Folder 842)
  - Guyana - Follow-up Correspondence (Box 108, Folder 843)
  - Haiti - Advisers Reports (Box 108, Folder 844)
  - Haiti - Documents (Box 108, Folder 845)
  - Haiti - Follow-up Correspondence (Box 108, Folder 846)
  - Haiti - Country Reports (Box 108, Folder 847)
  - Haiti - Briefing Books (Box 108, Folder 848)
  - Haiti - Country Reports (Box 109, Folder 849)
  - Haiti - NAR Memo (Box 109, Folder 850)
  - Honduras - NAR Notes (Box 109, Folder 851)
  - Honduras - Briefing Books (May 1969) (Box 109, Folder 852)
  - Honduras - Advisers Reports (Box 109, Folder 853)
  - Honduras - Documents (Box 109, Folder 854)
  - Honduras - Follow-up Correspondence (Box 109, Folder 855)
  - Honduras - Country Reports (Box 109, Folder 856)
  - Honduras - Briefing Books (Box 110, Folder 857)
  - Jamaica - Documents (Box 110, Folder 858)
  - Jamaica - NAR Notes (Box 110, Folder 859)
  - Jamaica - Country Reports (Box 110, Folder 860)
  - Jamaica - Follow-up Correspondence (Box 110, Folder 861)
  - Jamaica - Briefing Books (Box 110, Folder 862)
  - Mexico - Follow-up Correspondence (Box 110, Folder 863)
  - Mexico - Country Reports (Box 110, Folder 864)
  - Mexico - Documents (Box 111, Folder 865)
  - Mexico - Adviser Reports (Box 111, Folder 866)
  - Mexico - Published Documents (Box 111, Folder 867)
  - Mexico - Briefing Books (Box 111, Folder 868)
  - Mexico - NAR Notes (Box 111, Folder 869)
  - Nicaragua - Advisers Reports (Box 111, Folder 870)
  - Nicaragua - Guest Lists (Box 111, Folder 871)
  - Nicaragua - Documents (Box 111, Folder 872)
  - Nicaragua - Follow-up Correspondence (Box 111, Folder 873)
  - Nicaragua - NAR Notes (Box 112, Folder 874)
  - Nicaragua - Country Reports (Box 112, Folder 875)
  - Nicaragua - Briefing Books (Box 112, Folder 876)
  - Panama - Schedules (Box 112, Folder 877)
  - Panama - Follow-up Correspondence (Box 112, Folder 878)
  - Panama - Documents (Box 112, Folder 879)
  - Panama - Documents (Box 112, Folder 880)
  - Panama - Documents (Box 113, Folder 881)
  - Panama - Documents (Box 113, Folder 882)
  - Panama - Country Reports (Box 113, Folder 883)
  - Panama - Briefing Books (Box 113, Folder 884)
  - Panama - NAR Notes (Box 113, Folder 885)
  - Paraguay - Country Reports (Box 114, Folder 886)
  - Paraguay - Briefing Books (Box 114, Folder 887)
  - Paraguay - NAR Notes (Box 114, Folder 888)
  - Paraguay - Follow-up Correspondence (Box 114, Folder 889)
  - Paraguay - Advisers Reports (Box 114, Folder 890)
  - Paraguay - Documents (Box 114, Folder 891)
  - Paraguay - Documents (Box 114, Folder 892)
  - Peru - Briefing Books (Box 115, Folder 893)
  - Trinidad and Tobago - Advisers Reports (Box 115, Folder 894)
  - Trinidad and Tobago - Documents (Box 115, Folder 895)
  - Trinidad and Tobago - NAR Notes (Box 115, Folder 896)
  - Trinidad and Tobago - Briefing Books (Box 115, Folder 897)
  - Trinidad and Tobago - Follow-up Correspondence (Box 115, Folder 898)
  - Trinidad and Tobago - Country Reports (Box 115, Folder 899)
  - Uruguay - Advisers Reports (Box 116, Folder 900)
  - Uruguay - Documents (Box 116, Folder 901)
  - Uruguay - Follow-up Correspondence (Box 116, Folder 902)
  - Uruguay - Country Reports (Box 116, Folder 903)
  - Uruguay - NAR Notes (Box 116, Folder 904)
  - Uruguay - Briefing Books (Box 116, Folder 905)
  - Venezuela - Briefing Books (Box 116, Folder 906)
  - Venezuela - Documents (Box 116, Folder 907)
  - Master Key of Outside Reports (Box 117, Folder 908)
  - Special Briefing Report - Agriculture, special reports by country, T. F. Carroll (Box 117, Folder 909)
  - Special Briefing Report - Aid to Latin America, U.S. Aid to L.A., Funding a Revolution, George Lodge (Box 117, Folder 910)
  - Special Briefing Report - Argentina in 1969, I and II, James Rowe (Box 117, Folder 911)
  - Special Briefing Report - Brazil Briefing Paper, William Simonson (Box 117, Folder 912)
  - Special Briefing Report - Chile, Chilean Political System, Robert Kaufman (Box 117, Folder 913)
  - Special Briefing Report - Colombia, A Background Report, James Payne (Box 117, Folder 914)
  - Special Briefing Report - Ecuador, USAID Programs and Policies, Lisa Lekis (Box 117, Folder 915)
  - Special Briefing Report - Labor, Selected Comments on LAbor in LAtin America, James Morris (Box 117, Folder 916)
  - Special Briefing Report - LAFTA, LA Integration and LAFTA, Arpad von Lazar (Box 117, Folder 917)
  - Special Briefing Report - Mexico, Recent U.S.-Mexico Relations, James Wilkie (Box 117, Folder 918)
  - Special Briefing Report - Military, Militarism in Latin America, Nancy Hoplei (Box 117, Folder 919)
  - Special Briefing Report - Military, U.S. Military Assistance to Latin America, Peter Krogh (Box 117, Folder 920)
  - Special Briefing Report - Organization of American States (OAS), Memorandum, Godfrey Harris (Box 117, Folder 921)
  - Special Briefing Report - Trade, A Critique of Free Trade, Robert Baldwin (Box 117, Folder 922)
  - Special Briefing Report - Trade, U.S. Policies toward Developing Countries, Raymond Mikesell (Box 117, Folder 923)
  - Special Briefing Report - Paraguay, Nacy Hoepli (Box 118, Folder 924)
  - Special Briefing Report - Venezuela, Background Paper, John Martz (Box 118, Folder 925)
  - Advisory Reports, Chronological (Box 118, Folder 926)
  - Advisory Reports, Alphabetical by Author (Box 118, Folder 927)
  - Advisory Reports, Miscellaneous (Box 118, Folder 928)
  - Advisory Reports, Alphabetical by Country (Argentina-El Salvador) (Box 118, Folder 929)
  - Advisory Reports, Alphabetical by Country (Guatemala-Uruguay) (Box 118, Folder 930)
  - Advisory Reports, Alphabetical by Subject (Box 119, Folder 931)
  - Trip I - Manifests (Box 119, Folder 932)
  - Trip II - Room Lists (Box 119, Folder 933)
  - Trip II - Manifests (Box 119, Folder 934)
  - Trip III - Manifests (Box 119, Folder 935)
  - Trip III - Room Lists (Box 119, Folder 936)
  - Schedules - Beebe, George (Box 119, Folder 937)
  - Schedules - Borella, Victor (Box 119, Folder 938)
  - Schedules - Butler, William (Box 119, Folder 939)
  - Schedules - Bronheim, David (Box 119, Folder 940)
  - Schedules - Bronk, Detlev (Box 119, Folder 941)
  - Schedules - Camp, John (Box 119, Folder 942)
  - Schedules - Cannon, James (Box 119, Folder 943)
  - Schedules - Cunningham, Evelyn (Box 119, Folder 944)
  - Schedules - Deaver, John (Box 119, Folder 945)
  - Schedules - Eckholm, Gordon (Box 119, Folder 946)
  - Schedules - Goldwater, Robert (Box 119, Folder 947)
  - Schedules - Gotaas, Harold (Box 119, Folder 948)
  - Schedules - Gould, Samuel (Box 119, Folder 949)
  - Schedules - Harris, Alan (Box 119, Folder 950)
  - Schedules - Hightower, John (Box 119, Folder 951)
  - Schedules - Hitt, Patricia (Box 119, Folder 952)
  - Schedules - Holland, George (Box 119, Folder 953)
  - Schedules - Hoving, James (Box 119, Folder 954)
  - Schedules - Howard, Frederick (Box 119, Folder 955)
  - Schedules - Johnston, John (Box 119, Folder 956)
  - Schedules - Kampmann, Flora (Box 119, Folder 957)
  - Schedules - Levinson, Jerome (Box 119, Folder 958)
  - Schedules - Marusi, Augustine (Box 119, Folder 959)
  - Schedules - McHugh, Dorothy (Box 119, Folder 960)
  - Schedules - McClellan, Andrew (Box 119, Folder 961)
  - Schedules - Miller, Allan (Box 119, Folder 962)
  - Schedules - Mrak, Emil (Box 119, Folder 963)
  - Schedules - Noel, James (Box 120, Folder 964)
  - Schedules - Porter, Robert (Box 120, Folder 965)
  - Schedules - Rabin, Kenneth (Box 120, Folder 966)
  - Schedules - Morrow, Hugh (Box 120, Folder 967)
  - Schedules - Reynolds, Clark (Box 120, Folder 968)
  - Schedules - Riland, Walter (Box 120, Folder 969)
  - Schedules - Watson, Arthur (Box 120, Folder 970)
  - Schedules - Wehrle, Leroy (Box 120, Folder 971)
  - Schedules - Wharton, Clifton (Box 120, Folder 972)
  - Schedules - Wheeler, Monroe (Box 120, Folder 973)
  - Schedules - Wolf, Thomas (Box 120, Folder 974)
  - Schedules - Woods, George (Box 120, Folder 975)
  - Schedules - Zuckerman, Hyman (Box 120, Folder 976)
  - Draft 7 (Box 120, Folder 977)
  - Statistics (Box 120, Folder 978)
  - Recommendations (Box 120, Folder 979)
  - Final Report - Print Orders (Box 120, Folder 980)
  - Recommendations - Organization (Box 120, Folder 981)
  - Bills (Box 120, Folder 982)
  - NAR Letters to Latin American Embassies on Final Report (Box 120, Folder 983)
  - Memos to James Cannon (Box 120, Folder 984)
  - Research Thank-you Letters (Box 120, Folder 985)
  - Walter G. Thompson Correspondence (Box 120, Folder 986)
  - Foul-Ups (Box 120, Folder 987)
  - Final Master List for Follow Up (Box 120, Folder 988)
  - Guatemala - Correspondence and Reports (Box 121, Folder 989)
  - No Answer Follow-up Letters (Box 121, Folder 990)
  - Transcript of Meeting with NAR and Advisors, June 20, 1969 (Box 121, Folder 991)
  - Adviser Reports (Box 121, Folder 992)
  - Transcript of NAR Briefing to Subcommittee on Western Hemisphere Affairs (Box 121, Folder 993)
  - Background Report on Latin America (Box 121, Folder 994)
  - Conversations with Leaders of Twenty American Republics (Box 121, Folder 995)
  - Transcripts and Reports of Presidential Mission to Latin America (Box 122, Folder 997)
    - Transcripts of Conference on Latin American Mission - Seal Harbor, Maine (Box 122, Folder 996)
  - Drafts of Quality of Life in the Americas Report (Box 122, Folder 998)
  - Press Conference with President, October 31, 1969 (Box 122, Folder 999)
  - Summary of Trip IV (Box 122, Folder 1000)
  - Members of Mission (Box 122, Folder 1001)
  - Letters to Heads of State (Box 122, Folder 1002)
  - Letters to American Ambassadors (Box 122, Folder 1003)
  - Staff Meetings - Mission (Box 122, Folder 1004)
  - Political Relations (Box 123, Folder 1005)
  - Haiti, July 1-2, 1969 (Box 123, Folder 1006)
  - Haiti - General Correspondence (Box 123, Folder 1007)
  - Memorandum of Haitian Government (Box 123, Folder 1008)
  - Haiti - Background Information, PEP (Box 123, Folder 1009)
  - Haiti - Political Situation (Box 123, Folder 1010)
  - Trip IV - Manifests (Box 123, Folder 1011)
  - Trip IV - Room Lists (Box 123, Folder 1012)
  - Background Materials and Translations of Quality of Life in the Americas (Box 123, Folder 1013)
  - Reports - Central American Common Market and Reforma Agraria en la Repblica Argentina (Box 124, Folder 1014)
  - Letters and Documents Received on Latin American Trip (Box 124, Folder 1015)
  - Adviser Reports (Box 124, Folder 1016)
  - Correspondence List (Box 124, Folder 1017)
  - Correspondence (A) (Box 124, Folder 1018)
  - Correspondence (B) (Box 124, Folder 1019)
  - Correspondence (C) (Box 125, Folder 1020)
  - Correspondence (D) (Box 125, Folder 1021)
  - Correspondence (E) (Box 125, Folder 1022)
  - Correspondence (F) (Box 125, Folder 1023)
  - Correspondence (G) (Box 125, Folder 1024)
  - Correspondence (H) (Box 125, Folder 1025)
  - Correspondence (I) (Box 125, Folder 1026)
  - Correspondence (J) (Box 125, Folder 1027)
  - Correspondence (K) (Box 125, Folder 1028)
  - Correspondence (L) (Box 126, Folder 1029)
  - Correspondence (M) (Box 126, Folder 1030)
  - Correspondence (N) (Box 126, Folder 1031)
  - Correspondence (O) (Box 126, Folder 1032)
  - Correspondence (P) (Box 126, Folder 1033)
  - Correspondence (Q) (Box 126, Folder 1034)
  - Correspondence (R) (Box 126, Folder 1035)
  - Correspondence (S) (Box 126, Folder 1036)
  - Correspondence (T) (Box 127, Folder 1037)
  - Correspondence (U) (Box 127, Folder 1038)
  - Correspondence (V) (Box 127, Folder 1039)
  - Correspondence (W) (Box 127, Folder 1040)
  - Correspondence (X-Z) (Box 127, Folder 1041)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - Latin American Mission, May 11-19, 1969 (Box 127, Folder 1042)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - Latin America Background Report (Box 127, Folder 1043)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - General Information (Box 127, Folder 1044)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - Fact Sheets (Box 127, Folder 1045)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - Costa Rica (Box 127, Folder 1046)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - El Salvador (Box 128, Folder 1047)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - Guatemala (Box 128, Folder 1048)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - Honduras (Box 128, Folder 1049)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - Mexico (Box 128, Folder 1050)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - Mexico (Box 129, Folder 1051)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - Nicaragua (Box 129, Folder 1052)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - Panama (Box 129, Folder 1053)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - Panama (Box 129, Folder 1054)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - Rolfe's ICC Special Study (Box 129, Folder 1055)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - News Release (Box 130, Folder 1056)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - Bolivia (Box 130, Folder 1057)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - Colombia (Box 130, Folder 1058)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - Brazil (Box 130, Folder 1059)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - Brazil (Box 130, Folder 1060)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - Uruguay (Box 131, Folder 1061)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - Paraguay (Box 131, Folder 1062)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - Paraguay (Box 131, Folder 1063)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - Argentina (Box 131, Folder 1064)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - Argentina (Box 132, Folder 1065)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - Mission Information, June 29-July 6, 1969 (Box 132, Folder 1066)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - Jamaica (Box 132, Folder 1067)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - Jamaica (Box 132, Folder 1068)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - Haiti (Box 133, Folder 1069)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - Haiti (Box 133, Folder 1070)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - Dominican Republic (Box 133, Folder 1071)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - Trinidad (Box 133, Folder 1072)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - Barbados (Box 134, Folder 1073)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - Guyana (Box 134, Folder 1074)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - General Material and Financial Report (Box 134, Folder 1075)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - Working Papers (Box 134, Folder 1076)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - News Conference, November 10, 1969 (Box 134, Folder 1077)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - Latin American Mission (Box 134, Folder 1078)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - Women (Box 134, Folder 1079)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - Haiti (Box 134, Folder 1080)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - Rockefeller Mission to Haiti (Box 135, Folder 1081)
  - Arthur K. Watson Files - Working Papers (Box 135, Folder 1082)
  - Country Report - Argentina (Box 135, Folder 1083)
  - Country Report - Barbados (Box 135, Folder 1084)
  - Country Report - Bolivia (Box 135, Folder 1085)
  - Country Report - Brazil (Box 135, Folder 1086)
  - Country Report - Colombia (Box 135, Folder 1087)
  - Country Report - Costa Rica (Box 136, Folder 1088)
  - Country Report - Dominican Republic (Box 136, Folder 1089)
  - Country Report - Ecuador (Box 136, Folder 1090)
  - Country Report - El Salvador (Box 136, Folder 1091)
  - Country Report - Guyana (Box 136, Folder 1092)
  - Country Report - Haiti (Box 136, Folder 1093)
  - Country Report - Honduras (Box 136, Folder 1094)
  - Country Report - Jamaica (Box 137, Folder 1095)
  - Country Report - Mexico (Box 137, Folder 1096)
  - Country Report - Mexico (Education, Tourism) (Box 137, Folder 1097)
  - Country Report - Mexico (Economy, Transportation) (Box 137, Folder 1098)
  - Country Report - Mexico (Crime, Housing) (Box 137, Folder 1099)
  - Country Report - Mexico (Health, Recreation) (Box 137, Folder 1100)
  - Country Report - Nicaragua (Box 137, Folder 1101)
  - Country Report - Panama (Box 138, Folder 1102)
  - Country Report - Paraguay (Box 138, Folder 1103)
  - Country Report - Trinidad and Tobago (Box 138, Folder 1104)
  - Country Report - Uruguay (Box 138, Folder 1105)
  - Report - Quality of Life in the Americas (Box 138, Folder 1106)
  - Report - Reply to the Rockefeller Report on the Mission to South and Central America (Box 138, Folder 1107)
  - Extra Copies - Country Reports - Argentina (Box 138, Folder 1108)
  - Extra Copies - Country Reports - Barbados (Box 139, Folder 1109)
  - Extra Copies - Country Reports - Bolivia (Box 139, Folder 1110)
  - Extra Copies - Country Reports - Brazil (Box 139, Folder 1111)
  - Extra Copies - Country Reports - Colombia (Box 139, Folder 1112)
  - Extra Copies - Country Reports - Costa Rica (Box 140, Folder 1113)
  - Extra Copies - Country Reports - Dominican Republic (Box 140, Folder 1114)
  - Extra Copies - Country Reports - El Salvador (Box 140, Folder 1115)
  - Extra Copies - Country Reports - Ecuador (Box 140, Folder 1116)
  - Extra Copies - Country Reports - Ecuador (Box 141, Folder 1117)
  - Extra Copies - Country Reports - Guyana (Box 141, Folder 1118)
  - Extra Copies - Country Reports - Guatemala (Box 141, Folder 1119)
  - Extra Copies - Country Reports - Haiti (Box 141, Folder 1120)
  - Extra Copies - Country Reports - Honduras (Box 142, Folder 1121)
  - Extra Copies - Country Reports - Jamaica (Box 142, Folder 1122)
  - Extra Copies - Country Reports - Mexico (Box 142, Folder 1123)
  - Extra Copies - Country Reports - Nicaragua (Box 142, Folder 1124)
  - Extra Copies - Country Reports - Nicaragua (Box 143, Folder 1125)
  - Extra Copies - Country Reports - Panama (Box 143, Folder 1126)
  - Extra Copies - Country Reports - Paraguay (Box 143, Folder 1127)
  - Extra Copies - Country Reports - Uruguay (Box 143, Folder 1128)
  - Correspondence - Professor Kleinman (Box 143, Folder 1129)
  - Via del Mar, CECLA (also Quality of Life in the Americas first draft) (Box 143, Folder 1130)
  - Latin American Report thank-you notes (Box 144, Folder 1131)
  - American Thank-yous for Latin America Report (Box 144, Folder 1132)
  - American Thank-yous for Latin America Report (Box 144, Folder 1133)
  - NAR Notes (Box 144, Folder 1134)
  - NAR Memos and Drafts (Box 144, Folder 1135)
  - Dominican Republic Thank-you Letters (Box 144, Folder 1136)
  - Alliance for Progress (Box 145, Folder 1137)
  - Treaty on Art Exports (Box 145, Folder 1138)
  - Alliance for Progress Hearings (Box 145, Folder 1139)
  - Inter-American Development Bank (Box 145, Folder 1140)
  - Senate Foreign Relations (Box 145, Folder 1141)
  - Guillermo Belt Correspondence (Box 145, Folder 1142)